<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="storyContents">
<!--        <item>-->
<!--            Rich Dad Poor Dad is about Robert Kiyosaki and his two dads—his real father (poor dad) and the father of his best friend (rich dad)—and the ways in which both men shaped his thoughts about money and investing. He says that his poor dad went to Stanford and earned a Ph.D., and his rich dad never finished the eighth grade. The book consists of 8 chapters, lessons that everyone must learn. The central message conveyed by Kiyosaki is that you don’t need to earn a high income to be rich.He says that many are too afraid of being branded as a weirdo, in order to exit the rat race. People let the two main emotions everyone has around money dominate our decisions which are fear and greed. He says this is the reason people should not just look for a job as no job is safe anymore. Example- If you get a raise in a job you should invest the extra money in stocks or fund that increases your income but because of the fear that we may lose some money by investing in these assets, many people resist investing.The other opinion is when greed takes you over, a person might take the extra money that he/she receives from a raise and spend it on stuff that he doesn’t need like buying a fancy car and the payments for that car will eat up your money. These lessons tell us how important it is for us to be educated financially, the burden of this lies on the person itself as no school teaches us this.-->
<!--        </item>-->
        <item>
            Tenali Rama was known for his sense of humor. In fact, king Sri Krishnadevaraya used to enjoy his witty remarks even when they were targeted at him. Here is one such story about Tenali Rama and Arab horse.

Sri Krishnadevaraya was said to be fond of horses. He used to have a fine collection of them in his stables and would always look to add rare breeds from across the world to his collection.One day, an Arabian horse trader visited the king’s courtroom and informed him that he had brought the finest horse from Arabia. He requested the king to see the horse.

Sri Krishnadevaraya examined the horse, and it was indeed a magnificent creature! He immediately expressed his interest in buying it. The trader then said, “Your majesty, I have two more such horses with me in Arabia, and it would be my pleasure to bring them to you.”

The king, who was much impressed by the horse, agreed to buy the other two horses as well and paid the trader 5,000 gold coins as an advance for the rest of the horses. The trader took the money and promised to return with the horses.

Months passed, but there was no sign of the trader. This began to trouble the king. To ease his mind, he went on a walk in the royal gardens. There, he spotted Tenali Rama sitting under a tree and scribbling something on a piece of paper. The curious king asked Rama what he was writing.

Tenali Rama stopped writing and showed the king the paper. It was a list of names with the king’s name at the top. On the top of the list was written “List of the Biggest Fools in Vijayanagara Kingdom.”

The king became furious and asked Rama for an explanation. Rama replied, “Apologies for adding you to the list, your majesty. Unfortunately, it is true! How could your highness trust a stranger, give him a huge sum of money, and expect him to return?To counter his argument, the king asked, “What if he really comes back?” To this, Raman replied, “Then he will be the first name in the list…” and laughed.

The king laughed at this witty remark and embraced Rama for easing his tension with his humor.
        </item>
        <item>
            Once Emperor Akbar became very angry at his favorite minister Birbal. He asked Birbal to leave the kingdom and go away. Accepting the command of the Emperor, Birbal left the kingdom and started working in a farmer’s farm in an unknown village far away under a different identity.

As months passed, Akbar started to miss Birbal. He was struggling to solve many issues in the empire without Birbal’s advice. He regretted a decision, asking Birbal to leave the empire in anger. So Akbar sent his soldiers to find Birbal, but they failed to find him. No one knew where Birbal was. Akbar finally found a trick. He sent a message to the head of every village to send a pot full of the wit to the Emperor. If the pot full of wit can not be sent, fill the pot with diamonds and jewels.

This message also reached Birbal, who lived in one of the villages. The people of the village got together. All started talking about what to do now? The wit is not a thing, which can be filled in the pot. How will we arrange for diamonds and jewels to fill the pot and send to the Emperor? Birbal who was sitting among the villagers said, “Give me the pot, I will fill the wit in one month’s end”. Everyone trusted Birbal and agreed to give him a chance. They still didn’t know his identity.

Birbal took the pot with him and went back to the farm. He had planted watermelons on his farm. He selected a small watermelon and without cutting it from the plant, he put that in the pot. He started looking after it by providing water and fertilizer regularly. Within a few days, the watermelon grew into a pot so much that it was impossible to get it out of the pot.

Soon, the watermelon reached to the same size as the pot from inside. Birbal then cut the watermelon from the vine and separated it with the pot. Later, he sent a pot to Emperor Akbar with a message that “Please remove the wit without cutting it from the pot and without breaking the pot”.

Akbar watched the watermelon in the pot and realized that this can only be Birbal’s Work. Akbar himself came to the village, took Birbal back with him.
        </item>
        <item>
Once upon a time, there lived a greedy lion in the jungle who attacked and killed animals. With the result every animal in the jungle was very afraid of him. One day they all decided that each animal would go to the lion as his prey. The lion agreed to this and soon animals were in queue. Finally, it was the rabbit’s turn. Where, they decided to send the wise old one. The rabbit traveled slowly and reached the lion’s den before the sunset. The lion furiously asked him, ‘Why are you late?’ The rabbit answered, ‘A group of rabbits were coming to you. But on their way they were attacked by another ferocious lion. I somehow managed to escape and reached her. The other’s are still stuck.’ And then he also told the lion that the other lion was challenging him.Upon hearing this the lion got extremely angry. He asked the rabbit to take him to meet the new lion. The wise rabbit took the lion to a deep well and showed his own reflection in the water of the well. When the lion growled the reflection did the same. He considered his reflection to be his enemy. This enraged him and finally he jumped into the well to attack the other lion and by doing so he ended his own life. Thus, the wise old rabbit saved all the animals in the forest.        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time there lived a monkey named Red-face on a tree by the side of the sea. The tree was an apple tree and the fruits it bore were sweet as nectar. Once a crocodile named Ugly-Mug swam ashore and Red-face threw apples at him and asked him to taste them. Ugly-Mug started coming everyday ashore and eat the fruits thrown by Red-face and soon they became good friends. Ugly-Mug used to take some fruits to his home to his wife.The crocodile returned the next day. And the next. And the next one after that. Soon the two became very good friends. They discussed their lives, their friends and family, like all friends do. The crocodile told the monkey that he had a wife and that they lived on the other side of the river. So the kind monkey offered him some extra rose apples to take home to his wife. The crocodile’s wife loved the rose apples and made her husband promise to get her some every day.Meanwhile, the friendship between the monkey and the crocodile deepened as they spent more and more time together. The crocodile’s wife started getting jealous. She wanted to put an end to this friendship. So she pretended that she could not believe that her husband could be friends with a monkey. Her husband tried to convince her that he and the monkey shared a true friendship. The crocodile’s wife thought to herself that if the monkey lived on a diet of rose monkeys, his flesh would be very sweet. So she asked the crocodile to invite the monkey to their house.The crocodile was not happy about this. He tried to make the excuse that it would be difficult to get the monkey across the river. But his wife was determined to eat the monkey’s flesh. So she thought of a plan. One day, she pretended to be very ill and told the crocodile that the doctor said that she would only recover if she ate a monkey’s heart. If her husband wanted to save her life, he must bring her his friend’s heart.So the crocodile went to the rose apple tree and invited the monkey to come home to meet his wife. He told the monkey that he could ride across the river on the crocodile’s back. The monkey happily agreed. As they reached the middle of the river, the crocodile began to sink. The frightened monkey asked him why he was doing that. The crocodile explained that he would have to kill the monkey to save his wife’s life. The clever monkey told him that he would gladly give up his heart to save the life of the crocodile’s wife, but he had left his heart behind in the rose apple tree. He asked the crocodile to make haste and turn back so that the monkey could go get his heart from the apple tree.

        </item>
        <item>
Once upon a time there lived a sparrow with her husband on a tree. She had built a nice nest and laid her eggs in the nest. One morning, a wild elephant with spring fever feeling restive came to the tree in search of shade and in a rage broke the branch of the tree on which the nest was residing. Unluckily all the sparrow eggs were lost though both parents were saved. The she-sparrow was deep in lament.Seeing her lament, the woodpecker bird, a friend of hers offered her consolation that she would think of a way of killing the elephant. Then she went to her friend the gnat, who in turn went to the counselor frog for advice. The frog then devised a scheme for killing the elephant. He asked the gnat to buzz in the ears of the elephant, so that the elephant would be thrilled to listen to the music of the gnat and close its eyes.Seeing her lament, the woodpecker bird, a friend of hers offered her consolation that she would think of a way of killing the elephant. Then she went to her friend the gnat, who in turn went to the counselor frog for advice. The frog then devised a scheme for killing the elephant. He asked the gnat to buzz in the ears of the elephant, so that the elephant would be thrilled to listen to the music of the gnat and close its eyes.Then she asked the woodpecker to pluck his eyes. She herself would be on the edge of a pit and would croak misleading the elephant to think that it is a pond. The next day at noon the three carried out the plan and the elephant was killed when he fell flat into a pit after being blinded by the woodpecker when he closed his eyes in response to the gnat. So the revenge was taken with collective wit of all three animals.        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time there lived a heron by the side of a pond. It was a lazy creature and once devised a plan to get a supply of fish without doing much work. So one day, he went to the side of the pond and put on a gloomy face without attempting to catch any fish. The pond was also inhabited by a crab, which was wise and often helped the fish in the pond. On seeing the gloomy heron, the crab asked her what the matter was.The heron said, "Alas! I am worried that the pond is going to be soon devoid of any fish, which are in turn my source of food. I overheard a group of fishermen talking about catching all the fish in this pond. But I know of a pond somewhat far away, where all the fish shall be safe.If the fish are interested, i can carry a few each day to the other pond where they will be safe."
All the fish were eager to make use of the heron in reaching a safer destination. So everyday some of them volunteer to go with the heron. The heron took some fish each day in the beak, and on reaching a large rock used to eat all the fish up and leave the bones of the fish at the rock.If the fish are interested, i can carry a few each day to the other pond where they will be safe."
All the fish were eager to make use of the heron in reaching a safer destination. So everyday some of them volunteer to go with the heron. The heron took some fish each day in the beak, and on reaching a large rock used to eat all the fish up and leave the bones of the fish at the rock.So she was able to get a continuos supply of fish at no effort at all. In the end, the curiosity got the better of the crab, and one day it volunteered to go with the fish. When it had gone closer to the rock, it realised the foul play the heron had been playing on the poor fish. Enraged, it tightened its claws around the neck of the heron and snapped the head of the heron off. The heron died a selfish death. The crab crept back to the pond and told all the fish about the lies the heron had been telling.
        </item>
        <item>
            A lion named Karalakesara was living in a forest, loyally served by Dhoosaraka, a jackal that used to accompany the lion wherever he went. One day, an elephant badly injured the lion in a fight. The injuries were so serious that the lion could not go out hunting. As a result, the jackal also had to go without food. Both the master and the servant became very weak. Unable to bear hunger, the jackal pleaded with the lion to get him some food."You know my plight. I cannot move out of this place. However, if you manage to lure some animal to come here, I will kill him and both of us can have a good meal," said the lion. So, the jackal set out in search of some animal and saw a donkey feeding himself on weeds. The jackal approached him and said, "O my friend, please accept my regards. I have not seen you for a long time. You have become very weak. What is the reason?"
The donkey said in sad tones, "How shall I tell you my suffering? The washerman is tormenting me by placing too much weight on my back. He does not feed me at all. I exist on weeds. That is why my body is weak."The jackal said, "If that is the case, why don't you come with me? I shall show you a place where you can have your heart's fill of green and fresh grass. We can happily spend our time there.""You have given me good news. But there is a problem. We are domestic animals and you are all wild animals. One of them will certainly kill me," said the donkey whose name was Lambakarna.Allaying his fears, the jackal said, "O uncle, don't say like that. This place is in my control. Nobody can enter this area. Just like you are suffering at the hands of the washerman, there are three female donkeys in this area, which are waiting for a suitable husband. They are all young and told me, "If you are really our uncle, go and get a suitable husband for us." It is on that mission I have come here and seen you."
The donkey replied, "If that is the case, let's go now."

        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time, there lived two friends in a village. One of them was sharp and selfish while the other was innocent and selfless. They were living in abject poverty. So, one day they decided to try their luck in some other city. They set off on a journey to materialize their dreams. They passed through a forest. Chatting and laughing, they covered most of the journey peacefully. Once or twice they were in danger but they faced the dangers manfully. But one of the incidents proved that fair-weather friends leave in the lurch. One day when they were passing through a thick part of the forest, they came across a bear. The sharp and selfish friend took to his heels and climbed up a tree, leaving his friend in danger. But the other one could not find time to climb up a tree.In the listlessness of despair, he lay on the ground and held his breath. He pretended to be dead and started praying to God for his life. The bear sniffed him from head to toe, but he did not move at all considering him dead, the bear left him unharmed and went away into the forest. When the bear was well out of sight, the first friend climbed down the tree and came to his friend he asked in mocking tone what the bear was saying into his ear. The friend, who was grieved at the selfishness of his friend disliked his tone. He replied angrily that the bear advised him never to trust a fair-weather friend who always leaves in the lurch. So, be careful in making friends. With these words, he said his friend goodbye forever and went away alone to reach his destination.


        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time there lived a priest who was extremely lazy and poor at the same time. He did not want to do any hard work but used to dream of being rich one day. He got his food by begging for alms. One morning he got a pot of milk as part of the alms. He was extremely delighted and went home with the pot of milk. He boiled the milk, drank some of it and put the remaining milk in a pot. He added slight curds in the pot for converting the milk to curd. He then lay down to rest.He was extremely delighted at the pot of milk he found and started dreaming about the pot of curd while he lay asleep. He dreamt that if he could become rich somehow all his miseries would be gone. His thoughts turned to the pot of milk he had set to form curd. He dreamt on : "By morning the pot of milk would set, it would be converted to curd. I would churn the curd and make butter from it. I would heat the butter and make ghee out of it. I will go to that market and sell that ghee, and make some money. With that money i will buy a hen. The hen will lay many eggs which will hatch and there will be many more hens and cocks. These cocks and hen will in turn lay hundreds of eggs and I will soon have a poultry farm of my own." He kept on imagining."I will sell all the hens of my poultry and buy some cows, and open a milk dairy. All the town people will buy milk from me. I will be very rich and soon I shall buy jewellery. The king will buy all the jewellery from me. I will be so rich that I will be able to marry an exceptionally beautiful girl from a rich family. Soon I will have a handsome son. If he does any mischief I will be very angry and to teach him a lesson, I will hit him with a big stick." During this dream, he involuntarily picked up the stick next to his bed and thinking that he was beating his son, raised the stick and hit the pot. The pot of milk broke and he awoke from his sleep. Only then did he realise he was daydreaming.
        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time there was a sage and his wife. They lived near a river. The sage was a very kind hearted person but both sage and his wife were unhappy because they had no children.

One day as the sage was closing his eyes and doing meditation. At that time a kite dropped a baby girl mouse in the lap of the sage. The sage who was deeply engaged in meditation got up with a shock. He saw a mouse in his lap.The sage was very happy to see the mouse and thought that the god must have sent the mouse to him. He decided to take the mouse to his home and take good care of the mouse.

The sage and his wife decided to look after the mouse as their daughter. The sage with his extraordinary powers changed the mouse into a beautiful girl. Both sage and his wife took good care of the girl as their daughter. Time passed and the girl grew into a beautiful young girl of sixteen years old. The sage’s wife decided to get her daughter married. She requested her husband to look for a suitable groom for their daughter. The sage accepted what his wife said.

The sage started looking for a suitable groom for his daughter. He thought the Sun god would be the perfect match for his daughter.  The sage prayed for the Sun God to marry his daughter. But his daughter refused to marry the sun god and said, “ Dear father, I cannot marry the sun god. He is too hot. I will be reduced to ashes because of his heat.”Her father was very disappointed. He asked the sun god to suggest a suitable groom for his daughter. The Sun God said, “ Probably the lord of clouds would be a perfect match to your daughter as only a cloud can stop the rays of the sun.”
        </item>
        <item>
            Once A large herd of elephants lived in a jungle. Their king was a huge, majestic tusker. He looked after them with love and care. A severe drought hit the area. As there was no rain for a few years, all the rivers and tanks had dried up. Birds and animals died of thirst. The wild elephants suffered for want of water. Their king knew that if they did not get water soon, many of them would die of thirst. He had to find water as quickly as possible. He asked the elephants to go in different directions to look for water.
One of them found a large lake full of water in another jungle far away. The king was happy. He ordered all the elephants to make their way to the lake. It was a beautiful lake. Close to it was a colony of rabbits. The elephants had to pass through this colony. Thousands of rabbits were trampled to death and thousands more were injured. The rabbits were in a panic. Their king called a meeting. "A herd of wild elephants is passing through our colony," he said. "They have already killed or injured thousands of us. We have to take urgent steps to prevent more deaths. I want all of you to think of a way to save our race." The rabbits thought and thought. How could they stop the elephants? One little rabbit stood up. "Your Majesty," he said, "if you will send me as your messenger to the king of the elephants, I may be able to find a solution." "By all means, go as my messenger and see what you can do." The little rabbit hurried out. He saw a group of elephants returning from the lake. Right in the middle was the king. To get near him was impossible. "I will be crushed to death,' thought the rabbit. So he climbed up a huge rock. "O, king of the elephants," he shouted, "hear me, please." The king heard his voice and turned towards him.
        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time there lived a partridge under a tree. The partridge one day decided to go to the fields and indulge itself in the food there. But it did not return for many days as it found the fields a good source of food.In the meantime a hare came along one day and occupied the same dwelling which the partridge used to live in. The partridge however returned from the fields having grown plump from the food. It wanted to claim the dwelling for itself. A fight ensued and the hare was saying that the dwelling belonged to whoever occupied it.Then they both decided to contact a supposedly learned cat, on the shores of the Ganges who was supposed to be wise and old. So one day they both approached the cat with their problem. The cat, which was actually a hypocrite who earned his livelihood by posing as a priest, decided to take advantage of the occasion. On hearing the partridge and the hare from a distance, it said, "Sorry! I can't hear you from that far a distance because of old age. Dont worry I mean no harm to you. Come closer and both of you relate your stories." They were fooled into coming near and as soon as he could lay his hands on both of them he killed them both and had a meal.
        </item>
<!--        <item>-->
<!--            Louisa was slow and still in her movements; it took her a long time to prepare her tea; but when ready it was set forth with as much grace as if she had been a veritable guest to her own self. The little square table stood exactly in the centre of the kitchen, and was covered with a starched linen cloth whose border pattern of flowers glistened. Louisa had a damask napkin on her tea-tray, where were arranged a cut-glass tumbler full of teaspoons, a silver cream-pitcher, a china sugar-bowl, and one pink china cup and saucer. Louisa used china every day — something which none of her neighbors did. They whispered about it among themselves. Their daily tables were laid with common crockery, their sets of best china stayed in the parlor closet, and Louisa Ellis was no richer nor better bred than they. Still she would use the china. She had for her supper a glass dish full of sugared currants, a plate of little cakes, and one of light white biscuits. Also a leaf or two of lettuce, which she cut up daintily. Louisa was very fond of lettuce, which she raised to perfection in her little garden. She ate quite heartily, though in a delicate, pecking way; it seemed almost surprising that any considerable bulk of the food should vanish.-->
<!--        </item>-->
    </string-array>
</resources>